Brady J. Walsh

10 Berry Street #1112, North Andover, MA 01845 857-345-0602 | <u>bradywalsh@bradywalsh.me</u> | <u>bradywalsh.me</u>

SUMMARY

A self-motivated and organized professional with over 11 years' experience providing thorough and skillful technical support for a medium-scale agency. Creative problem solver with the ability to think outside the box and effectively resolve technical challenges. Uniquely able to learn new skills and quickly adapt to the ever-changing IT industry.

EDUCATION

Wentworth Institute of Technology, Boston, MA, 2014 - 2018

B.S., cum laude, in Computer Networking; minor in Computer Science

Bunker Hill Community College, Cambridge, MA, 2010 - 2013

Associates in Computer Science

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Self-Employed Consultant, Malden, MA 2018 – Current

Technical Consultant – Providing networking and software expertise to customers. Projects includes Migrating Web Servers from Windows Server 2003 to Windows Server 2012, developing custom containerized solutions for rapid deploy of WordPress servers and other Websites, moved onsite backups into the cloud.

Moviri, Inc., Boston, MA, 2018 - Current

IT Consultant — Works directly with customers implementing technologies and processes for the performance optimization of IT systems, quality control of services provided, Capacity Planning, Business Service Automation and IT Governance & Strategy, in line with the best practices such as the guidelines provided by ITIL. Developed custom ETL code for BMC's TrueSight Capacity Optimization and BMC's Helix Optimize. Enterprise Software support for various ETL connectors including SCOM, Splunk, Kubernetes, AppDynamics, and ServiceNow.

MASSACHUSETTS HEALTH CONNECTOR, Boston, MA, 2010 - 2018

IT Support Specialist – Reported to IT Process Manager, was responsible for providing desktop, network, voice and application support to Connector staff, as well as testing any new software builds and/or new technology that the Connector is working with. Prior to 2011 was an IT intern with similar responsibilities.

- · Assist in the management of IT hardware and software assets, including software patch management
- Assist in testing CCA software builds
- Responsible for documenting IT policies, procedures, and protocols
- Migrated on-premise infrastructure to the cloud

SKILLS

Technology

- Development Languages: Java, C#, Golang, Regex, SQL, PHP, Python, Javascript, Ruby, C, C++, Visual Basic
- Web Languages: HTML, CSS3, SASS, Coffee Script, Bootstrap, JQuery
- Web Frameworks: Apache, Nginx, LAMP, Jekyll, Gorilla/Mux, Ruby on Rails, NodeJS, MEAN
- Code Version Control: Git, GitHub, GitLab, Bitbucket, Subversion
- Databases: MySQL, SQL Server, SQLite, H2, Oracle, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, DB2
- Scripting Languages: Perl, Bash, Batch, Powershell, VB Script
- Office Software: Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Visio, OneNote, Project
- Operating Systems: Windows, Mac OSX, Linux, Unix, Solaris, AIX, IBM Main Frames
- Backup & Disaster Recovery: CloudBerry, Veeam, Barracuda Backup, AWS S3, Acronis, Carbon
- Networking Equipment: Cisco, Zyxel, TP-Link, Linksys, SonicWall, pfSense
- Cloud Technologies: AWS, Google Cloud, Azure, Heroku, Firebase
- IT Governance: ITILv3, COBIT
- Virtualization: VMware, VirtualBox, OpenStack, Docker, Kubernetes

INTERESTS

Security, Raspberry PI, Web Development, Traveling, Language Learning, and Cooking